(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
two years ago,
قبل عامين،
I got married to Miss Lan Hewei
تزوجت من الآنسة لان هيوي
from the Lanhe Group.
من مجموعة لانهي.
What?
ماذا؟
We planned to tell you
كنا نخطط لإخبارك
on our wedding day,
في يوم زفافنا،
but after the accident,
لكن بعد الحادث،
she fell into a coma.
دخلت في غيبوبة.
So,
لذا،
only a few people know about it.
لا يعرف عنها إلا عدد قليل من الناس.
But,
لكن،
fortunately, she's finally
لحسن الحظ، هي أخيراً
back by my side.
عاد إلى جانبي.
Now,
الآن،
let's welcome my wife,
فلنرحب بزوجتي،
Lan Hewei!
لان هيوي!
How did Lin Mojiao know I would come today?
كيف عرفت لين موجياو أنني سآتي اليوم؟
Honey,
عسل،
welcome home.
أهلاً بك في بيتك.
How did Lin Moqing
كيف فعل لين موكينغ
suddenly appear in Haicheng?
هل يظهر فجأة في هايتشنغ؟
Where has he been all these years?
أين كان طوال هذه السنوات؟
We only found that
لم نجد سوى ذلك
he came back from Southeast Asia.
لقد عاد من جنوب شرق آسيا.
But all traces of him there
لكن كل آثاره كانت هناك
have been erased.
تم مسحها.
We can't find any information.
لم نتمكن من العثور على أي معلومات.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
we also found that Mrs. Lin lost her memory.
كما وجدنا أن السيدة لين فقدت ذاكرتها.
I don't know how much she remembers.
لا أعرف كم تتذكر.
You're still alive!
ما زلت على قيد الحياة!
Lost her memory?
هل فقدت ذاكرتها؟
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
you finally came back.
لقد عدت أخيراً.
[Looks like]
[يبدو مثل]
[I have to play it by ear.]
[عليّ أن أتصرف وفقاً للظروف.]
Senior.
كبير.
Uncle, aunt.
عمي، عمتي.
You're quite something.
أنت شخص مميز للغاية.
You secretly married Lin Mojiao
لقد تزوجت سراً من لين موجياو
and got involved with Lin Moqing.
وانخرط في علاقة مع لين موكينغ.
I don't like you,
أنا لا أحبك،
but you can mess up
لكن يمكنك أن تخطئ
my marriage with Lin Mojiao.
زواجي من لين موجياو.
You're somewhat useful.
أنت مفيد إلى حد ما.
Miss Zhu.
الآنسة تشو.
take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
How dare you be happy?
كيف تجرؤ على أن تكون سعيداً؟
You can't even handle the marriage alliance of the Lin family.
لا يمكنك حتى التعامل مع تحالف الزواج لعائلة لين.
The Lan family took it away from you.
لقد أخذته عائلة لان منك.
Don't you know that?
ألا تعلم ذلك؟
You're useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة.
How dare you talk back?
كيف تجرؤ على الرد عليّ؟
You haven't learned anything good
لم تتعلم أي شيء جيد
overseas these years.
في الخارج هذه السنوات.
Go back to work at Churong tomorrow.
سأعود إلى العمل في تشورونغ غداً.
Why are you mad at the child?
لماذا أنت غاضب من الطفل؟
Surprise!
مفاجأة!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
This is my home.
هذا بيتي.
Shouldn't I come back?
ألا يجب أن أعود؟
Am I not welcome here?
ألا أُرحَّب بي هنا؟
I brought your wife
أحضرت زوجتك
back for you.
سأعود إليك.
How are you going to thank me?
كيف ستشكرني؟
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
what's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Senior,
كبير،
he saved me.
لقد أنقذني.
But I don't know him.
لكنني لا أعرفه.
I only knew
كنت أعرف فقط
we were married
لقد تزوجنا
after I saw
بعد أن رأيت
our marriage certificate.
شهادة زواجنا.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
If I had known you were my sister-in-law,
لو كنت أعلم أنكِ زوجة أخي،
I would have
كنت أود أن
hidden you away.
أخفاك بعيدًا.
Lin Moqing,
لين موكينج,
don't make such jokes with Vivi.
لا تطلق مثل هذه النكات على فيفي.
I'm not joking.
أنا لا أمزح.
She is beautiful
إنها جميلة
and gentle.
ولطيف.
I don't want her to come back.
لا أريدها أن تعود.
Senior
كبير
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Let's go upstairs to rest.
هيا بنا نصعد إلى الطابق العلوي لنرتاح.
Leave him alone.
اتركوه وشأنه.
He's always like this.
هو دائماً على هذه الحال.
Brother
أخ
You should treat her well.
يجب أن تعاملها معاملة حسنة.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I'll take her away.
سآخذها بعيداً.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
do you remember
هل تذكر
where Qing saved you?
أين أنقذك تشينغ؟
My head hurts.
رأسي يؤلمني.
I only remember...
لا أتذكر سوى...
Remember what?
أتذكر ماذا؟
Was it in the hospital?
هل حدث ذلك في المستشفى؟
When I was unconscious,
عندما كنت فاقداً للوعي،
someone wanted to take me away.
أراد أحدهم أن يأخذني بعيداً.
I wanted to shout,
أردت أن أصرخ،
but I couldn't.
لكنني لم أستطع.
Without you by my side,
بدونك بجانبي،
I was so scared.
كنت خائفاً جداً.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
apart from these,
وبصرف النظر عن هذه،
do you also forget the days
هل تنسى الأيام أيضاً؟
we were together?
كنا معًا؟
I can't remember.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر.
My head hurts.
رأسي يؤلمني.
It doesn't matter if you can't remember.
لا يهم إن لم تستطع التذكر.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
I didn't take good care of you before.
لم أعتنِ بك جيداً من قبل.
Now that you're back,
الآن وقد عدت،
I promise
أعدك
I won't let you get hurt.
لن أدعك تتأذى.
It's getting late.
لقد تأخر الوقت.
Let's get some rest.
لنأخذ قسطاً من الراحة.
Three,
ثلاثة،
two,
اثنين،
one.
واحد.
Maybe I caught a cold today.
ربما أصبت بنزلة برد اليوم.
I'm having a cold.
أنا مصاب بنزلة برد.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I was too hasty.
كنت متسرعاً للغاية.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
He's suspecting me.
إنه يشك بي.
She came back at the same time as Lin Moqing.
لقد عادت في نفس وقت عودة لين موكينغ.
And she lost her memory.
وفقدت ذاكرتها.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
I know the situation.
أنا على دراية بالوضع.
I can unlock it.
أستطيع فتحه.
Is it my phone?
هل المشكلة في هاتفي؟
Only one person.
شخص واحد فقط.
Z.
مع.
Senyuan Hospital.
مستشفى سينيوان.
VIP Room 01 on the third floor.
غرفة كبار الشخصيات رقم 01 في الطابق الثالث.
Senyuan Hospital...
مستشفى سينيوان...
It's the same hospital in the report.
إنه نفس المستشفى المذكور في التقرير.
T Country...
تي كانتري...
Who is Z?
من هو Z؟
He must know something.
لا بد أنه يعلم شيئاً.
I've known the situation.
كنت على دراية بالوضع.
How could Lin Moqing have Meng?
كيف استطاع لين موكينغ أن يمتلك مينغ؟
She's safe for now.
هي بأمان في الوقت الحالي.
Lin Moqing can be trusted.
يمكن الوثوق بلين موكينغ.
Use him to cooperate with you.
استخدمه للتعاون معك.
Play it by ear.
تصرف حسب الظروف.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
I cooked noodles for you.
لقد طبخت لك المعكرونة.
Your face
وجهك
is all red.
كلها حمراء.
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
This noodle should be spicier next time.
يجب أن تكون هذه النودلز أكثر حرارة في المرة القادمة.
Okay.
تمام.
Today,
اليوم،
Lan Hewei went to the Lin family.
ذهب Lan Hewei إلى عائلة Lin.
Lan Hewei is with Lin Moqing
Lan Hewei مع Lin Moqing
and Lin Mojiao.
ولين موجياو.
You don't need to worry about her.
لا داعي للقلق بشأنها.
We grew up together.
لقد نشأنا معاً.
I can't just watch her walk into a trap.
لا أستطيع أن أشاهدها وهي تقع في الفخ.
She's Mrs. Lin now.
هي الآن السيدة لين.
What does it matter if you lose your status for her?
ما أهمية فقدان مكانتك من أجلها؟
Has she ever given you a second glance?
هل سبق لها أن ألقت عليك نظرة ثانية؟
You grew up together,
لقد نشأتما معاً،
but you were still abandoned.
لكنك مع ذلك كنت مهجورًا.
Listen,
يستمع،
you're just a dog to me now.
أنت مجرد كلب بالنسبة لي الآن.
If I hadn't saved you,
لو لم أنقذك،
you wouldn't even be worth that.
لن تكون حتى مساوياً لذلك.
I...
أنا...
Honey.
عسل.
You can't even sleep with your wife,
لا يمكنك حتى أن تنام مع زوجتك،
so you come here to vent.
إذن أنت تأتي إلى هنا لتفريغ غضبك.
You're useless, incompetent,
أنت عديم الفائدة، وغير كفؤ،
useless,
عديم الفائدة،
just like your mother,
تماماً مثل والدتك،
so useless.
عديم الفائدة تماماً.
Honey,
عسل،
I'm not useless. I'm not.
أنا لست عديم الفائدة. أنا لست كذلك.
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.
Trash.
نفاية.
I'm not useless.
أنا لست عديم الفائدة.
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.
No.
لا.
Lu Xing.
لو شينغ.
You've got some nerve.
لديك جرأة كبيرة.
You drank because of that woman.
لقد شربت بسبب تلك المرأة.
And you drank my most expensive wine.
وشربتَ أغلى أنواع النبيذ لدي.
You...
أنت...